Trying to get those AI agents working by
itself, but it's not working.
>> Well, let's see what it does.
>> So, what's also getting hype on X right
now, it's all about loop coding stuff,
and thanks to Matt Pocock is the kind of
like the leader of that trend because he
builds lucky skills for engineers. Real
research prototype here are the issues
implementation review. That's all
working on GitHub. So, basically he's
building software on GitHub actions.
>> I still prefer having my own setup on my
Mac mini, and I don't mean like open
claw or paperclip or whatever. Just have
cloud build the GitHub actions in your
own Python scripts, run it locally on
your Mac mini in your own network, and
use that to automate. It will save you a
lot of money, and you can just add
additional checks and and loops on
whatever you want, and you don't rely on
GitHub.
>> I I like GitHub as a central place of
everything to have all of the issues
come aboard, and then like the road map
stuff. I think I'm going to like migrate
like the Gen AI development directly on
GitHub side with that kind of workflow
because that's basically open source
now, and same thing for ship code. I
kind of like that aspect of it cuz again
like I can run like all of the
end-to-end test. Yeah, the problem is
I'm going to [__] burn my
subscription.
>> Yeah, and I'm still convinced that I
don't want to rely on external services
where I cannot control the final price.
I think Microsoft 365 it's it's totally
different, but they showed this.
Everybody bought Word and Office before
for like $200 per user, and you could
use it for as long as you want, but you
didn't go to the next version. You had
to buy it again, and now everybody's
using the Microsoft 365, and in July
they are raising the prices between 10
to 16% again. And if your full company
is relying on it, you don't have a
choice, a 16% increase is a lot.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, but I mean, if you vendor locked
in, you're vendor locked in, right?
>> Yeah, so now you can just build whatever
you want with AI.
Why are you going to rely on GitHub
actions?
>> And yeah, that was the whole loop
engineering thesis that was based on
this interview that was from him. And
then everywhere on the timeline, you
have people explaining how loops works.
>> Yeah, it's easy, yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Do check React.
>> So yeah, what a loop actually does.
Yeah, let's go. Find work and it will be
agent, check results, record what
happened, decide next move. Yeah. Thank
you. That's a loop, bro. Yeah, okay. So
maybe we should reuse against the agent
because Fable will come back Yeah, at
some point, I guess.
>> I had Fable like asking him one thing
and he deployed 231 agents.
>> Yeah. Yeah, like I showed you, right?
Like it it worked for 20, 30 minutes and
I had like 85 agents or something.
>> I don't know, man. And like almost 10
million amounts of tokens used.
>> I can't wait to have like a a proper
framework that's telling me, "Okay, this
is what you do. You do that. You follow
the rules. And now you can build your
software."
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> Not like having skills and sub-agent and
plugin connector. Please simplify
because yeah, we we still need the
guardrails and stuff that we can find
from a framework. Everyone is still
trying to figure it out anyway.
>> Loops and their cost and their fault
condition, miss one and the loop cost
more than its return. The task repeat, a
loop amortizes its setup across many
rounds. Verification is automated. The
loop needs something that can fill the
work without you in the room. The token
budget can accept the waste. The
technique scales with budget, which is
why it's reads obvious to people with
effectively free token and reckless to
people. Yeah, that's the problem. We are
not Peter Peter always like working at
Codex with like unlimited subscription.
That's the main problem. Like the budget
behind those loop are nuts.
>> Maybe that's why it's it it is their own
people who are constantly giving us
these options.
>> Yeah.
>> Like the raw loop and now this loop.
>> In a way, there is some good ideas of
behind it because it makes sense, right?
Like you you set up like the scope of
the issue and then you had your test and
until all of the test is passed passed,
then you have your loop and that's it
and then the task is not done. But like
Ultra code does that by itself.
>> Yeah, it does and you don't have any
influence on it. It just keeps on going
and when you think I ask a small
question, it goes on for 20 minutes.
>> Yeah.
>> I think there can be an issue here
because if you actually pay for all the
tokens and you have an infinite loop
that cannot fix itself.
>> Yeah, like
>> open hot rail for after three runs and
you still haven't fixed it, stop it.
Flag it, give me a push message.
>> Yeah, because like Ultra code on loop,
you're going to do that twice.
>> Yeah.
>> Who wins, who loses? A loop's favor,
whoever can spend actually who actually
benefit in practice, team with
repetitive machine check over work in
the budget to run it. Code base with
existing test suits, asking first teams
with multiple agent pattern already in
use. Who should skip it today? Solo
builders and on consumer plan, let's go.
Anyone working on code with no automated
verification and teams whose real
constraint is review capacity rather
than on typing speed. Is it better to
get AI coding program running locally? I
mean, that's what we already talked
about like couple of weeks ago like
about those open code and MS
orchestrator where you plan with the
paid model and then you execute with
like open open source model on your
local machine so you don't spend that
credit and you only pay for plans.
>> Yeah. And if you want to do it with a
competing of a competitor model right
now, it's really expensive. You need
that that PC that we just showed, the
AMD like 4 to 5K, have the knowledge how
to set it up and you can't run it fully
locally.
>> Yeah.
>> But if you have a big project, that
could that could be like a good
investment.
>> Yeah, that makes sense. And yeah, but
the problem also with the local models
right now like Quince 3.7, I don't think
you can run that on a Raspberry Pi.
>> No, no. You need like a bigger PC.
>> [__] we're going back to open cloud LMS
orchestration. I mean, do you see a
future with that? Like yeah, do you
think you're going to code with like
five agents and one orchestrator and
like five open
>> I prefer building my own orchestrator
because every time I updated one of
those, I was having issues.
>> Yeah, true. That's why Ship got Ship
should be orchestrator, man.
>> Yes.
>> And now that Cloud like Cloud Pi is
back, then it makes sense to use it
again.
>> Yeah.
>> So, what are we going to do?
>> to create loops and automation.
>> On a 5K Mac Mini?
>> Yeah.
>> of RAM?
>> No, 5K M5 laptop.
>> Yeah.
>> That's going to be That's going to be
Yeah, that's going to be fun. I I was
still waiting for Fable 5.
>> Well, if it comes back, I want to use it
for sure.
>> Yeah.
>> But I'm also waiting on the answer from
OpenAI.
>> Yes.
>> If they can have a similar model that
will not be banned, they will take a lot
of customers from Anthropic.
>> And it should be cheaper, too.
>> So, if they are listening right now,
make the price lower, please.
>> Yes, price lower, better model. The next
few weeks should be interesting. Is that
the conclusion? I think that's the
conclusion.
>> We are going to wait.
>> Let's go.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you so much, everyone from the
chat. Michal, thank you so much for your
time.
>> Thank you, too.
>> And yeah, see you next week. Bye.